...but I need help.
So Okumura-senpai is going to take
the pictures for my first cosrom!
Milky
Succubus
Like, cosplay pictures?
In that skimpy outfit?
And she wants to sell them?
And what the heck is a ‘Milky Succubus’?!
This is beyond weird!
You’re not, like, embarrassed?
I mean, I’m a little bit embarrassed, sure...
I thought you weren’t!
But, that won’t stop me and my desire to
show everyone how much I love Liliel!
Is that what this is about?
Showing you love her?
That’s it!
I should’ve guessed he would be this easy!
TOTALLY GETS IT NOW
Thank God he’s a weirdo otaku.
Huh?
Tachibana-san, you knew I was cosplaying Liliel, so...
Do you like Liliel?
Do you want to cosplay together?!
Please, she’s a famous supermodel.
There’s no way she’ll say yes.
Sure.
See? I told y-
WHAT?!
I’ll do it!
Lili x Miri
Really?!
Why wouldn’t I?
I’ll do anything if there’s a chance
it’ll make Senpai fall for me!
That, and...
I gotta keep my eye on this one!
Do you have a crush on anyone?
Like, a girl?
There was a way longer pause
before he answered this time.
And I bet that virgin might
look at her Liliel cosplay
and think he’s falling for her instead!
So, there’s only one thing for me to do!
Put on a costume and get him to fall for me first!
Okay!
I think you should try cosplaying Miriella.
You mean her demon friend?
Why can’t I be Liliel?
So you can take pictures with my Liliel cosplay!
You still read the manga?
I wanna cosplay Liliel.
Huh? But you’d make such a good Miriella.
Senpai likes Liliel, right?
So I wanna cosplay Liliel!
Why does him liking Liliel
make you want to cosplay her?
Because I like him,
and I want to cosplay the character he likes!
Not like I can tell her that...
B...
Because I like Liliel.
ME TOO!
Okay, you can have her!
I’ll need to adjust the costume,
so go ahead and try it on.
Actually, I’ll do Miriella.
What? Why?!
Hey, Senpai! Do you like Miriella?
Hell yeah I do!
I LOVE MIRIELLA
I love her love rivalry with Liliel,
and the cute and sexy flirting
she does with Ashford!
She knows he’ll never feel the same,
but still she carries a flame
for him in her pure heart!
She’s got a cute figure and a great ass,
and real otaku love a flat-chested lady!
You said you’d never cheat on Liliel!
Tig bitties would ruin her whole vibe, anyway.
Yeah, Liliel’s my waifu.
Miriella’s my imouto!
I don’t wanna be your goddamn sister!
Huh?
But, he at least thinks she’s sexy and cute,
so maybe I still have a chance!
Okay, Tachibana-san, can I measure you?
I’ll buy the materials after school!
Wait, you’re gonna make it?!
Yup! I make all my costumes!
I’ll need 30 cm of twill fabric,
Hold up, how long is this gonna take?
70 cm of stretch leather,
some duct tape and stretch thread...
Like, a month?
Let me think...
It doesn’t need much fabric, so...
I can finish it tonight!
Really?
Oh, good timing, Tachibana-san!
Can I take your bust measurement again?
Who’s this?
This is Ririsa, she was Liliel yesterday.
She stayed up all night sewing and
brought her gear to school to finish it for you.
I slept through class and
covered my bags with makeup,
so we’re all good!
So she’s the girl who slept through every period today...
I’m torn on if I want to put extra stitching on the top,
since the manga design is a
little different from the anime.
Is anyone even gonna care?
Of course they will!
A single stitch can change
the whole look of a garment!
The manga always shows
the nipple through the top,
so I’d want to put a stitch there,
but they leave that out from the anime.
But the anime is in color,
so following the anime
design might look more authentic!
Okay, wow.
Fans of the manga might really
care about that part of her design.
I want to make a cosplay that portrays
the character design from every angle,
so you look just like the character herself.
You have to bring the two-dimensional
into three dimensions...
Striving for that perfection is a real challenge!
But, that won’t stop me and my desire
to show everyone how much I love Liliel!
That’s kind of impressive.
Guess cosplay is tougher than I thought.
All finished!
Hold the hell up, you want me to wear this?!
That’s Miriella’s squad uniform.
Yup, that’s her sexiest outfit!
What the hell?!
That’s worse than being naked!
I can’t even do bikinis, let alone that!
Okay, I’ll go get changed into mine!
That one’s not any better!
You’re really gonna wear that?!
Yep!
She’s gonna be skimpy Liliel!
That’ll kill Senpai!
I can't lose to her.
I’ve gotta win him over before she does!
Whoa, nice underwear!
I didn’t wear it for you, okay?
Where’d you get it? It looks fancy.
It’s not fancy.
What’s wrong?
What the heck?!
Just so you know,
I’m NOT jealous of these big fat blobs, okay?!
What?!
You know how girls do that
with each other in manga?
It’s kinda hot.
What’s wrong with your brain?
Do you not have any friends?
Wait, seriously?
Also, could you stop calling me Tachibana-san?
Just call me Mikari.
Mikari-chan...
Mikari-chan!
What?
It makes us sound like friends! Mikari-chan!
If you don’t need me, then stop saying it!
Ririsa doesn’t have any friends?
Okay, Mikari-chan!
Ugh, stop!
Let’s do our makeup and get changed!
First, let’s cover up your moles.
Anything else we need to cover up?
Huh? Oh, I can handle that myself.
Mikari-chan, you’ve got one on your inner thigh!
What?!
We’re not gonna take any close-ups down there!
I think we should make that our first close-up!
What?! You’re not serious!
There!
EEP!
Warn me before you touch me there!
That was a cute ‘eep’.
Stop teasing me!
I think I’m done? Do I look okay?
You look perfect!
I don’t even recognize myself.
I really hope this gets Senpai
to see me in a new light...
I know he’ll never fall for me the way I am now.
I have to change!
You can look now, Senpai.
Senpai!
Are you okay?!
Yeah, just... had to do the old cliché.
You look incredible, Mikari!
Your Miriella is perfect!
Senpai is looking at me and gushing!
It’s a new milestone!
And Ri... Liliel, you’re looking perfect as always!
But his eyes went straight for Liliel!
I mean, duh, he likes Liliel,
but Miriella’s not bad, right...?
You know, I never liked his dumb manga,
but I always kinda liked Miriella.
She falls for Ashford after he rescues her,
and always tries to flirt with him,
but his heart’s already set on Liliel,
so she’ll never have him.
Why won’t you look at me?!
She eventually becomes
friends with Liliel,
but she never tells anyone how she feels.
She was so much like me.
I could never hate her.
Why won’t you look at me?!
That’s so Miriella!
Your delivery was perfect! I’m floored!
That’s such an iconic line.
What? I mean, I wasn’t trying to act it out or anything...
Whatever.
As long as I can get him to look at me like that...
S-so, senpai, you said you liked her ass?
What?! Uh, yeah.
W-what do you think... of me now?
I, uh...
Do you like me?
Hell yeah, I love you!
(Love Miriella, that is.)
Ten years of waiting,
and he finally says he loves me!
Ten long years I’ve waited to hear those words...
(She’s ignoring the context.)
For real, though...
This was all it took?
I waited ten years for this?
Whatever. I’m still glad I tried this!
Thanks, Miriella! And Ririsa, I guess.
Okay, let’s take some pictures for our cosrom!
We’re seriously gonna take pictures in these?
Yup!
Pretty sure my modeling contract says I can’t.
I won’t bother mentioning it.
I’m after Senpai’s attention, anyway.
You want me to pose like THAT?
We’re all ready to shoot!
If you get too embarrassed,
Mikari-chan, you can stop at any time.
Senpai and I can do the shoot without you!
And let them do it by themselves?!
I-I won’t need to stop!
I’d rather be embarrassed than let
Senpai fall in love with Ririsa!
Seriously, just say the word.
Stay focused!
I’m in double trouble now.
I can’t let myself feel anything from them!
This time, I’ll use my secret technique!
I’ll pretend to be the very man whose pure
intentions are never sullied by their seduction!
I myself will become Lord Ashford!
At the ready, Liliel, Miriella!
Y-yes, sir!
Now he’s getting into character, too?!
Let’s start with this pose, first!
LET ME HEAL YOU!
AHN!
The hottest scene between the two of them...
That’s right, the healing scene!
Why does she need to touch her tits to heal her?!
I mean, Liliel explains it in the manga.
Breasts are life-givers!
Holy tissue that bequeaths life energy to newborns!
So, you have to touch them for any life energy magic!
Because that makes perfect sense...
Okay, then... I’m gonna touch you now.
J-just be gentle, okay?
Calm down, Okumura!
Lord Ashford has never gotten
a boner for either of them!
Is this turning him on? Senpai’s into this?!
I had my doubts... But this might work!
Maybe she’s being TOO gentle!
T-that was so good, Mikari-chan!
Huh?
According to the manga,
mana infusion is supposed to feel orgasmic!
Is this porn?!
I got the perfect picture of your expression, Miriella!
I-I wasn’t roleplaying...
Senpai saw that just now?
And he took a picture of it?!
Okay, now you give me a mana infusion!
What?
Miriella thanks Liliel for the healing
by replenishing some of her mana.
How are you saying that with a straight face?
S-so I just have to do what you did, right?
Yup!
Oh my God, don’t moan!
She didn’t mean it, Miriella!
Mana infusions are orgasmic!
Wait, she was just pretending?
Well, okay...
Is this the power of a true mana infusion?!
Lord Ashford bore witness to this and stayed flaccid?
What a legend...
Senpai!
H-he’s getting way more turned on by Liliel...
Okay, do the infusion on me one more time!
Huh?! You want to redo those photos?
Don’t pull so hard!
What’s happening?!
O-our costumes are caught on each other!
Holy shit, is it happening?!
Senpai, please help!
It is! God dammit!
M-my chestpiece is caught on hers.
Okay, but...
Is she for real?!
She’s gonna make him help?!
No! If he helps Liliel, if he touches her...
But, if he doesn’t...
J-just do it.
Just do it already, Senpai!
I don’t want Ririsa’s costumes to tear!
Mikari-chan!
O-Okay!
Is this seriously happening to me again?!
Focus! No thoughts, head empty!
Lord Ashford would leap into action to save them!
Remember, they’re just heavy bags of sand.
God damn it all!
They don’t feel like sand at all!
Why are you crying, Senpai?!
It’s no use, Ririsa! I’ll break it if I pull on it!
Then can you unhook the straps under my armpit?
That’ll make it come apart!
W-wait, hold on, don’t unhook it, or...
Unhook the straps?
I see...
There was a downside to that plan.
Y’know, Lord Ashford doesn’t survive all his battles.
Senpai!
M-Mikari-chan! Hold on a sec...
So when Miriella says this,
she’s deciding to hide her feelings for
Ashford to protect her friendship with Liliel?
Yeah, that’s what I’m saying!
I thought it was obvious.
Yeah, it totally is!
You totally understand where
Miriella’s coming from, Mikari!
I’m sorry I never figured it out.
Huh?
Mikari, I should’ve known...
...you’re still a huge otaku!
What? No, I’ve never been a weirdo otaku!
I thought you’d forgotten all about the manga.
So, it’s been really fun talking about it with you again.
I get it now.
I was so desperate to get him to like me.
I never actually tried to get the things he liked.
Senpai wasn’t happy to see me dressed as Miriella.
He was happy because he thought
we both loved his favorite manga.
Cosplay brought me into the
world he loves so dearly.
W-well, thank you for taking
pictures with me, Mikari-chan!
Our cosrom is gonna be great!
Sorry, but you can’t use my pictures.
I’d be breaking my modeling contract.
Huh?
Sorry. Forgot to tell you.
So these all have to be shelved?!
Yeah, sorry. The pro model stuff is serious.
You just have to accept it.
I see why you like cosplay now, though.
I’d be cool doing it with you again.
Really?!
Because I had so much fun
doing a group cosplay with you!
Mikari?
I don’t need to rush. After all...
Senpai’s 3D, too. This might not be impossible.
Don’t worry ‘bout it.
What was I feeling just now?
I sure had fun today.
Too bad we can’t use the photos, though.
Senpai! Speaking of photos...
We actually have enough pictures
to put out a cosrom now!
Let’s put one together and sell it at a cosplay event!
It’s finally happening.
I’ve already applied for a table
at an event next month, but...
It’s during Golden Week.
So we’ve got a little over a week.
I’m really hoping we can make it...
We’ve got a whole week.
Editing takes a ton of time!
We have to touch up the pictures,
then code the HTML...
I can learn how to do it.
What? No, I’ll do it all myself! You don’t have to!
I said I would help, though.
Sure, but this is a lot of work.
And way more boring than taking pictures.
You’d hate it.
Ririsa, I didn’t say I’d only help out with the easy bits.
We’re doing this together, right?
That’s what I promised.
Senpai...
I-I know, but... I don’t know how
I could ever make it up to you.
You don’t have to.
I’ve been having tons of fun doing this with you!
O-okay! Then I’d love your help!
If we keep quiet during
the rounds at 10 and 2,
we can get away with working here overnight.
I got scared for a second!
Okay, let’s get started!
R-right!
First, let’s pick out the photos we want to use.
Once we find the best shot of each of the
poses that works with the cosrom theme,
we drag it into the app and adjust the color,
edit out any blemishes, just make it perfect.
And we’ll have to do that for about 500 photos.
Five hundred?!
Well, let’s get to it!
Yeah!
This is taking a lot longer than I thought.
Yeah.
If each one takes five minutes, then 500 is gonna take...
A while, Senpai.
Don’t give up.
It’s only 41 hours and 40 minutes.
Are you sure we’re gonna make it?
We’ve got this, Ririsa.
We should’ve started way earlier...
Or applied for the next event instead...
Don’t start saying that...
or you won’t be able to stop!
I know, but...
Don’t back down!
Together, we’ll make it happen!
Is someone in here?!
Crap!
If he gets in, I’ll pop out and apologize!
You stay hidden!
But-
Don’t worry, Ririsa. I’ve got you covered.
Okay, but... Senpai, you’re really close!
Damn keys.
Whatever.
He’s gone.
Okay, back to work, Ririsa!
Don’t worry, Ririsa. I’ve got you covered.
That’s right. He’s got me covered!
I’m not alone!
We’re going to make the best cosrom ever, together!
Time For Our First Event!